question_data = [
    {"category": "History",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2016, the United Kingdom voted to stay in the EU.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "California is larger than Japan.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
